Guide to the Jesse H. Jones Family and Personal Papers, 1841-2000 MS 252
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Personal (JHJ), 208250 (Box 16-92)
  - Subseries N: Public Service, 208699 (Box 26-56)
    - Federal Loan Administrator, 1941-49; 208983 (Box 31)
      - R.K. LeBlond, 1941; 208985 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Travel, 1941; 208986 (Box 32)
        - 1941, 208987 (Box 32, Folder 2)
        - Special train, 1941; 208988 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Public statements, 1941; 208989 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Moffett vs. Aramco, 1941-49; 208990 (Box 32)
        - United Kingdom loan, 1941; 208991 (Box 32, Folder 5)
        - James A. Moffett testimony, 1941-47; 208992 (Box 32, Folder 6)
        - Newsclippings, 1941-47; 208993 (Box 32, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence, 1941-48; 208994 (Box 32, Folder 8)
        - Jesse H. Jones affadavits, 1941-48; 208995 (Box 32, Folder 9)
        - Jesse H. Jones subpoenas, 1941-48; 208996 (Box 32, Folder 10)
        - Jesse H. Jones deposition, 1941-48; 208998 (Box 32, Folder 11)
        - Stenographer's minutes, 1941-48; 208997 (Box 32, Folder 12)
        - Memorandum, 1941-48; 209000 (Box 32, Folder 13)
        - Opinion, 1949; 209001 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson Senatorial campaign, 1941-50; 209002 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Secretary of Commerce, 1942-45; 209003 (Box 32)
      - Telephone and telegraph, 209004 (Box 32)
        - 1942-43, 209005 (Box 32, Folder 16)
        - 1944-45, 209006 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - FDR inauguration, 1944; 209007 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, 209008 (Box 32)
        - 1942-43, 209009 (Box 32, Folder 19)
        - Will Clayton, 1943; 209010 (Box 32, Folder 20)
        - FDR/Houston Chronicle, 1944; 209011 (Box 32, Folder 21)
        - 1944-45, 209012 (Box 33, Folder 1)
        - not dated, 209013 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Travel, 209017 (Box 33)
        - 1942-43, 209018 (Box 33, Folder 3)
        - 1944-45, 209019 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Public statements, 209020 (Box 33)
        - 1942, 209021 (Box 33, Folder 5)
        - Cecil B. deMille, 1942; 209022 (Box 33, Folder 6)
        - Vice President Henry A. Wallace, 1943; 209023 (Box 33, Folder 7)
        - 1943-45, 209024 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Resignation (JHJ), 1945; 209399 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 209025 (Box 33-40)
      - Appointments, 1933; 209026 (Box 33, Folder 10-11)
      - Democratic National Committee, 1933; 209027 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Chronological, 209028 (Box 34)
        - 1932-33, 209029 (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - 1933, 209030 (Box 35, Folder 1, Box 34, Folder 2-4)
        - 1940-43, 209400 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Alphabetical, 209031 (Box 35)
        - A, 209032 (Box 35, Folder 3)
        - Stockton Axson, 209033 (Box 35, Folder 4)
        - B, 209034 (Box 35, Folder 5)
        - Blanche Babcock, 1937; 209035 (Box 35, Folder 6)
        - James A. Baker, 1913; 209036 (Box 35, Folder 7)
        - Thomas H. Ball, 1916, 1919; 209037 (Box 35, Folder 8)
        - Bernard Baruch, 1924, 1933; 209038 (Box 35, Folder 9)
        - J. Russ Baty, 1940s-50s; 209039 (Box 35, Folder 10)
        - Norman Baxter, 1935; 209040 (Box 35, Folder 11)
        - Prue M. Baxter, 1950s; 209042 (Box 35, Folder 12)
        - J.C. Bering, 1923, 1925; 209043 (Box 35, Folder 13)
        - Clay Berry, 209044 (Box 35, Folder 14)
        - E.W. Bertner, 1933; 209045 (Box 35, Folder 15)
        - W.N. Blanton, 1933; 209041 (Box 35, Folder 16)
        - Sol Bloom, 1933; 209046 (Box 35, Folder 17)
        - J.H. Burnett, 1933; 209047 (Box 35, Folder 18)
        - Willard Burton, 1933; 209048 (Box 35, Folder 19)
        - C, 209049 (Box 36, Folder 1)
        - Amon Carter, 1930s-40s; 209050 (Box 36, Folder 2)
        - Bruce Carter, 1931, 1933; 209051 (Box 36, Folder 3)
        - Kenneth Cassidy, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 4)
        - W.B. Chew, 1907; 209052 (Box 36, Folder 5)
        - Bert Clark, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 6)
        - re: May Clark, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 7)
        - W.L. Clayton, 1931, 1933; 209053 (Box 36, Folder 8)
        - Ralph Cooley, 1933; 209054 (Box 36, Folder 9)
        - W.C. Costello, 1933, 1953; 209055 (Box 36, Folder 10)
        - E.L. Crain, 1935; 209056 (Box 36, Folder 11)
        - J.S. Cullinan, 1933; 209057 (Box 36, Folder 12)
        - D-E, 209058 (Box 36, Folder 13)
        - Josephus Daniels, 1933; 209059 (Box 36, Folder 14)
        - E.R. Deane, 209060 (Box 36)
          - 1914-38, 209061 (Box 36, Folder 15)
          - 1940-56, 209142 (Box 36, Folder 16)
        - R.C. Duff, 1925 (Box 36, Folder 17)
        - Joe Eagle, 1933; 209143 (Box 36, Folder 18)
        - Eisenhower, 1955-56; 209144 (Box 36, Folder 19)
        - Enid [?], 1915; 209145 (Box 36, Folder 20)
        - J.W. Evans, 1931, 1933; 209146 (Box 36, Folder 21)
        - F-G, 209147 (Box 36, Folder 22)
        - W.S. Farish, 1931, 1933; 209148 (Box 36, Folder 23)
        - J.A. Farley, 1933, 1936; 209149 (Box 36, Folder 24)
        - R.M. Farrar, 1914-14, 28, 33; 209150 (Box 36, Folder 25)
        - Ralph Feagin, 1931; 209151 (Box 36, Folder 26)
        - Henry Ferris, 1928-29; 209152 (Box 36, Folder 27)
        - Royal Ferris Jr., 1941; 209168 (Box 36, Folder 28)
        - Joseph Finger, 1931, 1933; 209169 (Box 36, Folder 29)
        - Alfred Finn, 1933, 1936; 209170 (Box 36, Folder 30)
        - W.W. Fondren, 1931, 1933; 209171 (Box 36, Folder 31)
        - Edsel Ford, 1931; 209172 (Box 36, Folder 32)
        - Zaidee Foster, 1929; 209173 (Box 36, Folder 33)
        - Kenneth Franzheim, 1925, 1933; 209174 (Box 36, Folder 34)
        - Frieda Freese, 1914; 209175 (Box 36, Folder 35)
        - J.W. Fullbright, 1950; 209176 (Box 36, Folder 36)
        - George Gallup, 1931; 209177 (Box 36, Folder 37)
        - John Garner, 1931, 1934; 209178 (Box 36, Folder 38)
        - Garrett/Booth, 1938, 1940s; 209250 (Box 36, Folder 39)
        - A.P. Giannini, 1933, 1935; 209179 (Box 36, Folder 40)
        - Carter Glass, 1930s; 209251 (Box 36, Folder 41)
        - Al Gore, Sr., 1944; 209252 (Box 36, Folder 42)
        - M/M John W. Graham, 1933; 209181 (Box 36, Folder 43)
        - H-J, 209182 (Box 36, Folder 44)
        - C.W. Harris, 1933; 209183 (Box 36, Folder 45)
        - Fred Heyne, 209184 (Box 36, Folder 46)
        - Maurice Hirsch, 1933; 209185 (Box 36, Folder 47)
        - Oveta C. Hobby, 1933; 209186 (Box 37, Folder 1)
        - William P. Hobby, 1933; 209187 (Box 37, Folder 2)
        - Oscar Holcombe, 1933; 209188 (Box 37, Folder 3)
        - Herbert Hoover, 1933, 1936; 209189 (Box 37, Folder 4)
        - Will Horowitz, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 5)
        - W.O. Huggins, 1915, 1920s; 209190 (Box 37, Folder 6)
        - Howard Hughes, 1921, 1930s; 209191 (Box 37, Folder 7)
        - Cordell Hull, 1933, 1935; 209192 (Box 37, Folder 8)
        - A.B. Jones, 1928-1950s; 209193 (Box 37, Folder 9)
        - John T. Jones, Jr., 1941, 1942, 1944, 1953-1954 (Box 37, Folder 10)
        - J.H. Jones family, 209253 (Box 37, Folder 11)
        - Mary Gibbs Jones, 1940s; 209401 (Box 37, Folder 12)
        - K-M, 209194 (Box 37, Folder 13)
        - J.H. Kirby, 1912; 209195 (Box 37, Folder 14)
        - J.M. Lawrence, 1906; 209196 (Box 37, Folder 15)
        - E.O. Lovett, 1933; 209197 (Box 37, Folder 16)
        - Harry Marx, 1927; 209198 (Box 37, Folder 17)
        - W.G. McAdoo, 1920, 1935; 209199 (Box 37, Folder 18)
        - Glenn McCarthy, 1950; 209200 (Box 37, Folder 19)
        - John Mecom, 1956; 209201 (Box 37, Folder 20)
        - Carol Merriam, 1933; 209202 (Box 37, Folder 21)
        - S.O. Moodie, 1933; 209203 (Box 37, Folder 22)
        - Henry Morgenthau, Jr., 1933; 209204 (Box 37, Folder 23)
        - W.W. Moore, 1932-33; 209205 (Box 37, Folder 24)
        - H.E. Morrow, 209206 (Box 37, Folder 25)
        - W.C. Munn, 1932-33; 209207 (Box 37, Folder 26)
        - N-R, 209208 (Box 37, Folder 27)
        - Jessie Nugent, 1915; 209209 (Box 37, Folder 28)
        - Adolph Ochs, 1929; 209210 (Box 37, Folder 29)
        - Drew Pearson, 1943, 1945; 209254 (Box 37, Folder 30)
        - E.A. Peden, 1933; 209211 (Box 37, Folder 31)
        - John Pershing, 1930s; 209212 (Box 37, Folder 32)
        - Hugh Potter, 1933; 209213 (Box 37, Folder 33)
        - F.C. Proctor, 1933; 209214 (Box 37, Folder 34)
        - John Radford, 1913; 209215 (Box 37, Folder 35)
        - H.B. Rice, 1907; 209216 (Box 37, Folder 36)
        - James Rockwell, 1932-33; 209217 (Box 37, Folder 37)
        - Rogers, 1930s; 209218 (Box 37, Folder 38)
        - Eleanor Roosevelt, 1933, 1941; 209219 (Box 37, Folder 39)
        - Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1933, 1940s; 209255 (Box 37, Folder 40)
        - Daniel Roper, 1933, 1935; 209220 (Box 37, Folder 41)
        - S-Z, 209221 (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - Peg Saffold, 1918; 209222 (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - Charles Schwab, 1935, 1937; 209223 (Box 38, Folder 3)
        - A.D. Simpson, 1933, 1943; 209224 (Box 38, Folder 4)
        - Alfred Smith, 1933; 209228 (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - A.D. Stewart, 1933; 209225 (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - S.W. Strauss, 1928-29; 209226 (Box 38, Folder 7)
        - Mark Sullivan, 209227 (Box 38, Folder 8)
        - Taub, 1930s, 1943; 209229 (Box 38, Folder 9)
        - Huston Thompson, 1926; 209230 (Box 38, Folder 10)
        - W.B. Trammell, 1933; 209231 (Box 38, Folder 11)
        - Harry Truman, 1935; 209232 (Box 38, Folder 12)
        - Louis Tuffly, 1933; 209233 (Box 38, Folder 13)
        - H.A. VanEaton, 1922; 209234 (Box 38, Folder 14)
        - Paul Wakefield, 1933, 1956; 209235 (Box 38, Folder 15)
        - Helen White, 1933; 209236 (Box 38, Folder 16)
        - Edith Wilson, 1935; 209237 (Box 38, Folder 17)
        - H.T.D. Wilson, 1913, 1918; 209238 (Box 38, Folder 18)
        - Gus Wortham, 1933; 209239 (Box 38, Folder 19)
        - unidentified, 209240 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Airplane accident, 209258 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Library of Congress, 209256 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - San Jacinto Monument, 209257 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - White House, 1943-45; 209315 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - President, 1943-45; 209316 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - 1939-43, 209317 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - On death of JHJ, 1956; 209247 (Box 39)
        - Sympathy letters, 1956; 209248 (Box 39, Folder 2)
        - Employee acknowledgments, 1956-57; 209249 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Houston Endowment related, 209318 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - undated, 209323 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Telegrams, 209324 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Personal stationery, 209241 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Invitations, 209242 (Box 39)
        - 1933, 209243 (Box 39, Folder 8, Box 40, Folder 1-3)
        - Embassy, 1940s; 209244 (Box 40, Folder 4)
        - White House, 1930s-40s; 209245 (Box 40, Folder 5)
        - Political, 210030 (Box 40, Folder 6)
        - Misc., 1940s; 209246 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Social/entertainment, 210031 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Contacts (index card files), 209483 (Box 41-55)
      - Business and personal, 209490 (Box 41-53)
        - A-Blaw, 1930s-40s; 209491 (Box 41)
        - Bleecker-Civilian, 1930-s40s; 209492 (Box 42)
        - Claffy-Donovan, 1930s-40s; 209493 (Box 43)
        - Doolin-Garvin, 1930s-40s; 209494 (Box 44)
        - Garwood-Hinga, 1930s-40s; 209495 (Box 45)
        - Hinkley-Kent, 1930s-40s; 209496 (Box 46)
        - Kenton-Means, 1930s-40s; 209497 (Box 47)
        - Mechanic-Newhouse, 1930s-40s; 209498 (Box 48)
        - Newlin-Reichmuth, 1930s-40s; 209499 (Box 49)
        - Reid-Skillern, 1930s-40s; 209500 (Box 50)
        - Skinker-Toner, 1930s-40s; 209501 (Box 51)
        - Toombs-Wolf, 1930s-40s; 209502 (Box 52)
        - Wolfe-Zuver, 1930s-40s; 209503 (Box 53)
      - Buildings, 1912-1940s; 209504 (Box 54-55)
        - Auditorium-Payrolls, 1912-1940s; 209505 (Box 54)
      - Political, 209506 (Box 55)
    - Publicity, 209507 (Box 56)
      - 1916, 209508 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - 1918-26, 209509 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - 1928, 209510 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - 1929, 209511 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - 1930-31, 209512 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - 1932-33, 209513 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - 1934-35, 209514 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - 1936, 209515 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - 1937, 209516 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - 1938, 209517 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - 1939, 209518 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - 1940, 209519 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - 1941, 209520 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - 1942-44, 209521 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - 1942-43, 209522 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - 1945-46, 209523 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - 1949, 209524 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - 1950-55, 209525 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - 1956, 209526 (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - Books, 209527 (Box 56)
        - Fifty Billion Dollars, 1951; 209528 (Box 56)
          - Review, 1951; 209529 (Box 56, Folder 20)
        - Jesse H. Jones: The Man and the Statesman, 1956; 209530 (Box 56)
          - Typescripts, 1954; 209531 (Box 56, Folder 21)
          - Reviews, 1956; 209532 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - Death, 1956; 209533 (Box 56-57)
        - Newsclippings, 1956; 209534 (Box 56, Folder 23, Box 57, Folder 1-3)
        - Estate, 1956; 209535 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - 1957-59, 209536 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - 1962, 209537 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - 1964, 209538 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Jones Hall, 1966; 209539 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - 1974-79, 209540 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - 1983-89, 209541 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - 1990-97, 209542 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Rice Hotel, 1994; 209543 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Houston Club, 1994; 209544 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - 2000s & undated, 209547 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - Oversize publications, 209545 (Box 58)
        - Jones Hall (Houston Chroncile special supplement), Sunday, Oct. 2, 1966 [2 copies], 209546 (Box 58)
        - RFC The House of Jesse, Fortune [11 copies], 1940; 209548 (Box 58)
        - The Gulf Building, 1929; 209549 (Box 58)
        - Jesse Holman Jones, Houston Post-Dispatch, 209550 (Box 58)
        - Beck Building Guide, Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, Houston Chronicle [3 copies], 2000; 209551 (Box 58)
        - Life, 1946; 209552 (Box 58)
        - KTRH, 209553 (Box 58)
        - Eastland Telegram, 1928; 209554 (Box 58)
        - Houston Post-Dispatch, 1920s; 209555 (Box 58)
        - unidentifed, 209556 (Box 58)
  - Subseries O: Statements, 209724 (Box 59)
    - 1928, 209728 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - I.L. Campbell, R.S. Sterling, 1928; 209730 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Will Hogg anti-Jones, 1928; 209733 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Subseries P: Speeches, 209735 (Box 59)
    - "Elements of Success," Southwestern University, 6/16/1925; 209737 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Texas Centennial Executive Committee, Ft. Worth, TX, 3/31/1928; 209741 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Testimonial dinner, Dallas, TX, 4/10/1928; 209744 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Texas Centennial, 1928; 209747 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - United States Commission for the Texas Centennial, Washington, DC, 8/17/1935; 209749 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Unveiling of state portrait, Austin, TX, 1935; 209752 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - "Texas--From San Jacinto to its Centennial," Advertising Club of New York, 4/21/1936; 209756 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Honoring Owen D. Young, Society of Arts & Sciences, NYC, 5/20/1936; 209757 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - "A Tribute to Gene Schacher", 6/12/1936; 209758 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - "General Robert E. Lee," unveiling of statue, Dallas, TX, 6/12/1936; 209759 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - "The Roosevelt Administration-Its Effect Upon and Relationship to Business," Washington, DC, 10/13/1936; 209760 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - "Roosevelt and Recovery," The Good Neighbor League of the Democratic National Committee, 10/23/1936; 209761 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Radio address, Democratic National Committee, Dallas, TX, 10/30/1936; 209762 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Conferment of the degree of Doctor of Law, A&M College of Texas, College Station, TX, 11/5/1936; 209764 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Laying of the cornerstone of the San Jacinto Memorial Monument, San Jacinto Battleground park, TX, 4/21/1937; 209765 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - 51st annual commencement of Temple University, Philadelphia, PA, 6/10/1937; 209766 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - National Association of Supervisors of State Banks, NYC, 10/8/1937; 209767 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Independent Petroleum Association of America at the Oil-World Exposition, Houston, TX, 10/14/1937; 209768 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - "Chicago's Salute to the Railroads," Fifth Annual Dinner of the Association of State Street Seniors of Chicago, Chicago, IL, 11/1/1937; 209769 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Washington Star broadcast over the Blue Network of the National Broadcasting Co., Washington, DC, 4/18/1938; 209770 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Annual Dinner of Chamber of Commerce, Lynchburg, VA, 4/21/1038; 209771 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Dedication of the Will Rogers Memorial Museum, Claremore, OK, 11/4/1938; 209772 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - American Bankers Association, Houston, TX, 11/15/1938; 209773 (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation 7-year report, Washington, DC, 2/2/1939; 209774 (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - "Tribute to Senator Carter Glass," Richmond, VA, 4/11/1940; 209775 (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - Committee for the Celebration of the President's Birthday for the National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, Washington, DC, 1/8/1942; 209776 (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - 30th annual meeting of the Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Chicago, IL, 4/30/1942; 209777 (Box 59, Folder 30)
    - Dedication of the Technological Institute of Northwestern University, Chicago, IL, 10/16/1942; 209778 (Box 59, Folder 31)
    - "The Dangers of Inflation," Mutual Broadcsting System, Washington, DC, 7/8/1942; 209779 (Box 59, Folder 32)
    - Army Day Dinner of the Military Order of the World War, NYC, 4/3/1943; 209780 (Box 59, Folder 33)
    - Committee for Economic Development, NYC, 4/14/1943; 209781 (Box 59, Folder 34)
    - Insurance Program of the United States Chamber of Commerce, Washington, DC, 4/28/1943; 209782 (Box 59, Folder 35)
    - Petroleum Rubber Drive Luncheon, Washington, DC, 5/5/1943; 209783 (Box 59, Folder 36)
    - National Aeronautic Association of the USA in Celebration of the Establishment of the US Airmail and Development of Commercial Aviation, Washington, DC, 5/15/1943; 209784 (Box 59, Folder 37)
    - Official Inspection of the Synthetic Rubber Plants Institute, West VA, 6/11/1943; 209785 (Box 59, Folder 38)
    - Reply to Vice President Wallace, Washington, DC, 7/5/1943; 209786 (Box 59, Folder 39)
    - Washington Evening Star Radio Forum, Washington, DC, 7/21/1943; 209787 (Box 59, Folder 40)
    - "Post War Problems," New York Board of Trade, NYC, 9/30/1943; 209788 (Box 59, Folder 41)
    - New York Financial Writers' Association, NYC, 6/2/1944; 209789 (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - Subseries Q: Interviews, 209790 (Box 60)
    - Alan Brinkley, 209791 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - David Ginsberg, 209792 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Ginzburg, 209793 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - William P. Hobby, Jr., 209794 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Ann Holmes, 209795 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Robert Hopkins, 209796 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Ida Klaus, 209797 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Sarah McClendon, 209798 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - John Murphy, 1996; 209799 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Dana Petri, 1997; 209800 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Fred Pontello, 1996; 209801 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Daisy Pontenza, 1996; 209802 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Joe Pratt, 209803 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Jim Rogers, 1996; 209804 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Eugene Slater, 1996; 209805 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - August Waites, 1997; 209806 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Willard Walbridge, 1996; 209807 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Louie Welch, 1996; 209808 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Harvey Wheeler, 1996; 209809 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Subseries R: Civic-related, 210021 (Box 61)
    - Woodrow Wilson, 210025 (Box 61)
      - Birthplace and museum, 210026 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Annuity, 1923; 210027 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - San Jacinto Battleground programs, 1936-39; 210028 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Jones Hall celebratory remarks [see also Realia box 85], 1997; 210029 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Re: Jesse Jones biography, 1990s; 210032 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Jesse Jones centennial celebration [see also Audo/visual boxes 91-92], 1998; 210033 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Jesse Jones documentary, "Brother, Can You Spare a Million?", 2000; 210034 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Subseries S: Photographs, 210060 (Box 61-78)
    - Family, 210061 (Box 61-66)
      - Elizabeth Jones [JHJ grandmother], 210072 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - William Hasque Jones & Laura Ann Holman Jones [JHJ parents], 210073 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Elizabeth "Lizzie" Jones Farthing, 210074 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Nancy Jones Hurt, 210075 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Ida Jones Garrett, 210076 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - John T. Jones, Sr., 210077 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - M.T. Jones, 210078 (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - Louisa Jones, 210079 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Jeannette Jones (?), 210080 (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - Will E. Jones (?), 210081 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - Tilford Jones, 210082 (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - Sallie Candler, 210083 (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - Augusta Jones (JHJ cousin), 210084 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Audrey Jones Beck, 210085 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Audrey L. Jones - John Beck wedding, 210086 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Audrey Jones Beck & others, 210087 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Audrey Jones Beck house, 3223 Inwood, Houston, TX, 210088 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Jones family, 210089 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Unidentified family, 210090 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - M.T. & Louisa Jones house, 2918 Main, Houston, TX, 210091 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Jones house, Springfield, TN, 210092 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Family cemetery plot, Springfield, TN, 210093 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Birchmonte, North Conway, NH, 210094 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Boat "Audrey", 210095 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - Mary Gibbs Jones, 210096 (Box 62-63)
        - Early, 210097 (Box 62, Folder 13)
        - Individual, 210098 (Box 62, Folder 14)
        - with others, 210099 (Box 63, Folder 1)
        - copies with locations of originals, 210100 (Box 63, Folder 2)
        - Texas A&M award, Aug. 1956; 210101 (Box 63, Folder 3)
        - award, Oct. 1956; 210102 (Box 63, Folder 4)
        - TWU honorary degree, 1958; 210103 (Box 63, Folder 5)
        - selling war bonds, May 1943; 210104 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Jesse H. Jones, 210105 (Box 63-64)
        - Early, 210108 (Box 63, Folder 7)
        - Informal, 210109 (Box 63, Folder 8)
        - Formal, 210113 (Box 63, Folder 9, Box 64)
        - Proofs, 210110 (Box 64, Folder 3)
        - with Mary Gibbs Jones, 210111 (Box 64, Folder 4)
        - with US Presidents & politicians, 210112 (Box 64, Folder 5)
        - with others, 210114 (Box 64, Folder 6)
        - Office [Binz Building?], ca. 1900; 210115 (Box 64, Folder 7)
        - Office [Banker's Mortgage Building], 1956; 210116 (Box 64, Folder 8)
        - Funeral, 1956; 210117 (Box 64, Folder 9)
        - Oversize, 210118 (Box 65)
        - Large oversize, 210155 (Box 66)
    - Individuals, groups, at events, 210338 (Box 67-70)
      - A, 210339 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - American Business Association group, 210340 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - American Red Cross groups, 210341 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Architects, 210342 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Aviation-related, 210343 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - B, 210344 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - A. Burton's yacht, 1936; 210345 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - C, 210346 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - California toll bridge inspection visit, 1936; 210347 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Cambria County [PA] Fair, 1936; 210348 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Howard Creekmore, 210349 (Box 67, Folder 11)